Guide to the Men's Basketball Game Film Collection, 1947-1996 UA.13.01.0005
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Men's Basketball Game Films
  - Georgia Tech, 1984 March 09
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: Reel 3, 1984 March 09; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 77, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1944)
  - North Carolina, 1984 March 10
    Duke win; score: 77-75; ACC Tournament, Greensboro, NC; Reel 2 missing
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 1, 1984 March 10; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 77, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1945)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 3, 1984 March 10; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 77, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1946)
  - Maryland, 1984 March 11
    Duke loss; score: 62-74; ACC Tournament, Greensboro, NC
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Reel 1, 1984 March 11; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 77, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1947)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Reel 2, 1984 March 11; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 77, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1948)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Reel 3, 1984 March 11; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 77, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1949)
  - Washington, 1984 March 18
    Duke loss; score: 78-80; NCAA Tournament, Pullman, Wash.
    - Duke vs. Washington: Reel 1, 1984 March 18; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 77, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1950)
    - Duke vs. Washington: Reel 2, 1984 March 18; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 77, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1951)
    - Duke vs. Washington: Reel 3, 1984 March 18; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 77, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1952)
    - Duke vs. Washington: Reel 4, 1984 March 18; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 77, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1953)
  - St. Louis, 1984 November 26
    Duke win; score: 97-64
    - Duke vs. St. Louis: Reel 1, 1984 November 26; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 78, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1954)
    - Duke vs. St. Louis: Reel 2, 1984 November 26; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 78, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1955)
    - Duke vs. St. Louis: Reel 3, 1984 November 26; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 78, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1956)
  - William & Mary, 1984 November 28
    Duke win; score: 92-60
    - Duke vs. William & Mary: Reel 1, 1984 November 28; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 78, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1957)
    - Duke vs. William & Mary: Reel 2, 1984 November 28; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 78, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1958)
    - Duke vs. William & Mary: Reel 3, 1984 November 28; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 78, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1959)
  - St. Joseph's, 1984 December 01
    Duke win; score: 59-46
    - Duke vs. St. Joseph's: Reel 1, 1984 December 01; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 78, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1960)
    - Duke vs. St. Joseph's: Reel 2, 1984 December 01; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 78, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1961)
    - Duke vs. St. Joseph's: Reel 3, 1984 December 01; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 78, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1962)
  - Appalachian State, 1984 December 05
    Duke win; score: 98-64
    - Duke vs. Appalachian State: Reel 1, 1984 December 05; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 78, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1963)
    - Duke vs. Appalachian State: Reel 2, 1984 December 05; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 78, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1964)
    - Duke vs. Appalachian State: Reel 3, 1984 December 05; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 78, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1965)
  - Virginia, 1984 December 08
    Duke win; score: 78-65
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Reel 1, 1984 December 08; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 78, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1966)
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Reel 2, 1984 December 08; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 78, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1967)
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Reel 3, 1984 December 08; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 78, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1968)
  - East Carolina, 1984 December 10
    Duke win; score: 80-64
    - Duke vs. East Carolina: Reel 1, 1984 December 10; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 73, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1969)
    - Duke vs. East Carolina: Reel 2, 1984 December 10; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 73, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1970)
    - Duke vs. East Carolina: Reel 3, 1984 December 10; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 73, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1971)
  - Massachusetts, 1984 December 12
    Duke win; score: 88-56
    - Duke vs. Massachusetts: Reel 1, 1984 December 12; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 73, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1972)
    - Duke vs. Massachusetts: Reel 2, 1984 December 12; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 73, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1973)
    - Duke vs. Massachusetts: Reel 3, 1984 December 12; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 73, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1974)
  - Davidson, 1984 December 17
    - Duke vs. Davidson: Reel 1, 1984 December 17; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 78, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1975)
    - Duke vs. Davidson: Reel 2, 1984 December 17; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 78, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1976)
    - Duke vs. Davidson: Reel 3, 1984 December 17; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 78, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1977)
  - Northwestern, 1984 December 19
    Duke win; score: 76-55
    - Duke vs. Northwestern: Reel 1, 1984 December 19; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 79, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1978)
    - Duke vs. Northwestern: Reel 2, 1984 December 19; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 79, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1979)
    - Duke vs. Northwestern: Reel 3, 1984 December 19; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 79, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1980)
    - Duke vs. Northwestern: Reel 4, 1984 December 19; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 79, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1981)
  - Colorado, 1984 December 21
    - Duke vs. Colorado: Reel 1, 1984 December 21; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 73, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1982)
    - Duke vs. Colorado: Reel 2, 1984 December 21; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 74, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1983)
    - Duke vs. Colorado: Reel 3, 1984 December 21; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 74, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1984)
  - Virginia, 1985 January 05
    Duke win; score: 63-58
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Reel 1, 1985 January 05; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 79, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1985)
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Reel 2, 1985 January 05; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 79, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1986)
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Reel 3, 1985 January 05; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 79, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1987)
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Reel 4, 1985 January 05; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 79, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1988)
  - East Carolina, 1985 January 09
    Duke win; score: 87-63
    - Duke vs. East Carolina: Reel 1, 1985 January 09; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 79, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1989)
    - Duke vs. East Carolina: Reel 2, 1985 January 09; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 79, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1990)
    - Duke vs. East Carolina: Reel 3, 1985 January 09; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 79, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1991)
    - Duke vs. East Carolina: Reel 4, 1985 January 09; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 79, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1992)
  - Washington, 1985 January 12
    Duke win; score: 71-59
    - Duke vs. Washington: Reel 1, 1985 January 12; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 79, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1993)
    - Duke vs. Washington: Reel 2, 1985 January 12; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 79, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1994)
    - Duke vs. Washington: Reel 3, 1985 January 12; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 79, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1995)
  - Maryland, 1985 January 14
    Duke loss; score: 76-78
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Reel 1, 1985 January 14; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 79, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1996)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Reel 2, 1985 January 14; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 79, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1997)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Reel 3, 1985 January 14; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 79, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1998)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Reel 4, 1985 January 14; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 80, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1999)
  - Wake Forest, 1985 January 17
    Duke loss; score: 89-91
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Reel 1, 1985 January 17; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 80, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2000)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Reel 2, 1985 January 17; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 80, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2001)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Reel 3, 1985 January 17; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 80, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2002)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Reel 4, 1985 January 17; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 80, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2003)
  - North Carolina, 1985 January 19
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 1, 1985 January 19; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 80, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2004)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 2, 1985 January 19; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 80, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2005)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 3, 1985 January 19; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 80, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2006)
  - NC State, 1985 January 23
    Duke loss; score: 71-89
    - Duke vs. NC State: Reel 1, 1985 January 23; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 80, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2007)
    - Duke vs. NC State: Reel 2, 1985 January 23; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 80, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2008)
    - Duke vs. NC State: Reel 3, 1985 January 23; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 80, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2009)
    - Duke vs. NC State: Reel 4, 1985 January 23; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 80, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2010)
  - Clemson, 1985 January 26
    Duke win; score: 100-83
    - Duke vs. Clemson: Reel 1, 1985 January 26; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 80, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2011)
    - Duke vs. Clemson: Reel 2, 1985 January 26; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 80, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2012)
    - Duke vs. Clemson: Reel 3, 1985 January 26; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 80, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2013)
  - Wake Forest, 1985 January 30
    Duke win; score: 76-70
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Reel 1, 1985 January 30; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 80, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2014)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Reel 2, 1985 January 30; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 80, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2015)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Reel 3, 1985 January 30; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 80, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2016)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Reel 4, 1985 January 30; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 81, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2017)
  - Harvard, 1985 February 04
    Duke win; score: 82-53
    - Duke vs. Harvard: Reel 1, 1985 February 04; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 81, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2018)
    - Duke vs. Harvard: Reel 2, 1985 February 04; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 81, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2019)
    - Duke vs. Harvard: Reel 3, 1985 February 04; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 81, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2020)
  - Georgia Tech, 1985 February 06
    Duke loss; score: 71-81
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: Reel 1, 1985 February 06; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 81, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2021)
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: Reel 2, 1985 February 06; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 81, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2022)
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: Reel 3, 1985 February 06; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 81, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2023)
  - Maryland, 1985 February 09
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Reel 1, 1985 February 09; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 81, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2024)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Reel 2, 1985 February 09; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 81, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2025)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Reel 3, 1985 February 09; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 81, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2026)
  - Stetson, 1985 February 13
    Duke win; score: 94-51
    - Duke vs. Stetson: Reel 1, 1985 February 13; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 81, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2027)
    - Duke vs. Stetson: Reel 2, 1985 February 13; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 81, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2028)
  - Notre Dame, 1985 February 16
    - Duke vs. Notre Dame: Reel 1, 1985 February 16; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 81, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2029)
    - Duke vs. Notre Dame: Reel 2, 1985 February 16; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 81, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2030)
    - Duke vs. Notre Dame: Reel 3, 1985 February 16; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 81, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2031)
    - Duke vs. Notre Dame: Reel 4, 1985 February 16; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 81, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2032)
  - NC State, 1985 February 20
    Duke loss; score: 66-70
    - Duke vs. NC State: Reel 1, 1985 February 20; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 82, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2033)
    - Duke vs. NC State: Reel 2, 1985 February 20; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 82, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2034)
    - Duke vs. NC State: Reel 3, 1985 February 20; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 82, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2035)
  - Georgia Tech, 1985 February 23
    Duke win; score: 67-62
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: Reel 1, 1985 February 23; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 81, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2036)
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: Reel 2, 1985 February 23; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 81, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2037)
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: Reel 3, 1985 February 23; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 82, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2038)
  - Clemson, 1985 February 27
    - Duke vs. Clemson: Reel 1, 1985 February 27; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 82, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2039)
    - Duke vs. Clemson: Reel 2, 1985 February 27; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 82, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2040)
    - Duke vs. Clemson: Reel 3, 1985 February 27; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 82, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2041)
  - North Carolina, 1985 March 02
    Duke loss; score: 68-78
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 1, 1985 March 02; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 82, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2042)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 2, 1985 March 02; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 82, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2043)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 3, 1985 March 02; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 82, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2044)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 4, 1985 March 02; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 82, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2045)
  - Maryland, 1985 March 08
    Duke win; score: 86-73; ACC Tournament, Atlanta, Ga.
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Reel 1, 1985 March 08; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 82, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2046)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Reel 2, 1985 March 08; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 82, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2047)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Reel 3, 1985 March 08; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 82, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2048)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Reel 4, 1985 March 08; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 82, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2049)
  - Georgia Tech, 1985 March 09
    Duke loss; score: 64-75; ACC Tournament, Atlanta, Ga.
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: Reel 1, 1985 March 09; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 82, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2050)
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: Reel 2, 1985 March 09; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 82, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2051)
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: Reel 3, 1985 March 09; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 82, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2052)
  - Pepperdine, 1985 March 15
    Duke win; score: 75-62; NCAA Tournament, Houston, Texas
    - Duke vs. Pepperdine: Reel 1, 1985 March 15; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 83, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2053)
    - Duke vs. Pepperdine: Reel 2, 1985 March 15; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 83, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2054)
    - Duke vs. Pepperdine: Reel 3, 1985 March 15; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 83, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2055)
  - Boston College, 1985 March 17
    Duke loss; score: 73-74; NCAA Tournament, Houston, Texas
    - Duke vs. Boston College: Reel 1, 1985 March 17; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 83, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2056)
    - Duke vs. Boston College: Reel 2, 1985 March 17; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 83, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2057)
    - Duke vs. Boston College: Reel 3, 1985 March 17; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 83, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2058)
    - Duke vs. Boston College: Reel 4, 1985 March 17; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 83, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2059)
  - William & Mary, 1985 November 26
    Duke win; score: 84-61
    - Duke vs. William & Mary: Reel 1, 1985 November 26; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 83, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2060)
    - Duke vs. William & Mary: Reel 2, 1985 November 26; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 83, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2061)
    - Duke vs. William & Mary: Reel 3, 1985 November 26; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 83, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2062)
  - East Carolina, 1985 December 02
    Duke win; score: 98-66
    - Duke vs. East Carolina: Reel 1, 1985 December 02; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 83, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2063)
    - Duke vs. East Carolina: Reel 2, 1985 December 02; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 83, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2064)
    - Duke vs. East Carolina: Reel 3, 1985 December 02; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 83, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2065)
  - Vanderbilt, 1985 December 04
    Duke win; score: 84-74
    - Duke vs. Vanderbilt: Reel 1, 1985 December 04; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 83, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2066)
    - Duke vs. Vanderbilt: Reel 2, 1985 December 04; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 83, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2067)
    - Duke vs. Vanderbilt: Reel 3, 1985 December 04; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 83, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2068)
  - Virginia, 1985 December 07
    Duke win; score: 72-64
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Reel 1, 1985 December 07; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 83, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2069)
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Reel 2, 1985 December 07; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 83, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2070)
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Reel 3, 1985 December 07; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 84, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2071)
  - Davidson, 1985 December 18
    Duke win; score: 69-52
    - Duke vs. Davidson: Reel 1, 1985 December 18; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 84, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2072)
    - Duke vs. Davidson: Reel 2, 1985 December 18; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 84, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2073)
    - Duke vs. Davidson: Reel 3, 1985 December 18; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 84, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2074)
    - Duke vs. Davidson: Reel 4, 1985 December 18; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 84, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2075)
  - Appalachian State, 1985 December 28
    Duke win; score: 88-46
    - Duke vs. Appalachian State: Reel 1, 1985 December 28; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 84, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2076)
    - Duke vs. Appalachian State: Reel 2, 1985 December 28; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 84, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2077)
    - Duke vs. Appalachian State: Reel 3, 1985 December 28; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 84, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2078)
    - Duke vs. Appalachian State: Reel 4, 1985 December 28; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 84, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2079)
    - Duke vs. Appalachian State: Reel 5, 1985 December 28; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 84, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2080)
  - Northwestern, 1985 December 30
    Duke win; score: 78-55
    - Duke vs. Northwestern: Reel 1, 1986 December 30; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 84, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2081)
    - Duke vs. Northwestern: Reel 2, 1986 December 30; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 84, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2082)
    - Duke vs. Northwestern: Reel 3, 1986 December 30; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 84, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2083)
    - Duke vs. Northwestern: Reel 4, 1986 December 30; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 84, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2084)
  - Maryland, 1986 January 04
    Duke win; score: 81-75
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Reel 1, 1986 January 04; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 84, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2085)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Reel 2, 1986 January 04; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 84, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2086)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Reel 3, 1986 January 04; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 84, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2087)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Reel 4, 1986 January 04; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 84, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2088)
  - St. Louis, 1986 January 08
    Duke win; score: 74-64
    - Duke vs. St. Louis: Reel 1, 1986 January 08; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 85, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2089)
    - Duke vs. St. Louis: Reel 2, 1986 January 08; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 85, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2090)
    - Duke vs. St. Louis: Reel 3, 1986 January 08; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 85, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2091)
    - Duke vs. St. Louis: Reel 4, 1986 January 08; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 85, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2092)
  - NC State, 1986 January 11
    - Duke vs. NC State: Reel 1, 1986 January 11; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 85, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2093)
    - Duke vs. NC State: Reel 2, 1986 January 11; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 85, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2094)
    - Duke vs. NC State: Reel 3, 1986 January 11; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 85, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2095)
    - Duke vs. NC State: Reel 4, 1986 January 11; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 85, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2096)
  - St. Joseph's, 1986 January 13
    Duke win; score: 87-66
    - Duke vs. St. Joseph's: Reel 1, 1986 January 13; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 85, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2097)
    - Duke vs. St. Joseph's: Reel 2, 1986 January 13; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 85, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2098)
    - Duke vs. St. Joseph's: Reel 3, 1986 January 13; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 85, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2099)
    - Duke vs. St. Joseph's: Reel 4, 1986 January 13; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 85, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2100)
  - Wake Forest, 1986 January 16
    Duke win; score: 92-63
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Reel 1, 1986 January 16; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 85, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2101)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Reel 2, 1986 January 16; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 85, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2102)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Reel 3, 1986 January 16; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 85, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2103)
  - North Carolina, 1986 January 18
    Duke loss; score: 92-95
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 1, 1986 January 18; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 85, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2104)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 2, 1986 January 18; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 85, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2105)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 3, 1986 January 18; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 85, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2106)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 4, 1986 January 18; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 86, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2107)
  - Georgia Tech, 1986 January 21
    Duke loss; score: 80-87
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: Reel 1, 1986 January 21; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 86, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2108)
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: Reel 2, 1986 January 21; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 86, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2109)
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: Reel 3, 1986 January 21; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 86, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2110)
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: Reel 4, 1986 January 21; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 86, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2111)
  - Maryland, 1986 January 25
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Reel 1, 1986 January 25; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 86, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2112)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Reel 2, 1986 January 25; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 86, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2113)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Reel 3, 1986 January 25; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 86, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2114)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Reel 4, 1986 January 25; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 86, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2115)
  - Harvard, 1986 January 27
    Duke win; score: 89-52
    - Duke vs. Harvard: Reel 1, 1986 January 27; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 86, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2116)
    - Duke vs. Harvard: Reel 2, 1986 January 27; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 86, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2117)
    - Duke vs. Harvard: Reel 3, 1986 January 27; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 86, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2118)
  - Clemson, 1986 January 29
    Duke win; score: 89-78
    - Duke vs. Clemson: Reel 1, 1986 January 29; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 86, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2119)
    - Duke vs. Clemson: Reel 2, 1986 January 29; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 86, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2120)
    - Duke vs. Clemson: Reel 3, 1986 January 29; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 86, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2121)
    - Duke vs. Clemson: Reel 4, 1986 January 29; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 86, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2122)
  - Wake Forest, 1986 February 01
    Duke win; score: 68-58
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Reel 1, 1986 February 01; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 86, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2123)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Reel 2, 1986 February 01; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 86, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2124)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Reel 3, 1986 February 01; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 87, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2125)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Reel 4, 1986 February 01; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 87, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2126)
  - Georgia Tech, 1986 February 09
    Duke win; score: 75-59
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: Reel 1, 1986 February 09; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 87, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2127)